hey cool kids can we stop calling other countries homogenous so this is a thing i see that happens
quite a bit because people say well maybe things can happen easier in other nations that are more
homogenous or smaller than they can happen in the u.s because we are like a varied nation of
individuals that are not necessarily aligned in the same way and i would actually push back on
that because if you go to any of these other nations they will tell you homogenous because
the thing that connects them might be that they're from this place but there are so many other factors
that actually for many of those people are much more important than their nationalism you know you
go to anywhere in the in them you go to anywhere on the continent and they are gonna name their tribe
you know like it's not just enough to be from nigeria yes the niger population is huge and they
ride for nigeria but they're also like yeah i'm yoruba or yeah i'm evil or yeah you understand what
i'm saying it just seems very colonialist to me because it looks at another place and says look
they're all the same when if you are from that place it's very clear that they're not and for the
record people look at america and say look they're all the same so if you think they aren't looking at
us like homogeneic worldwide gentrifiers because that's what we are then you're missing it side note
you're not an expat you're an immigrant imagine saying mexico is homogeneic like that's crazy like
in mexico yes there's going to be people who share a pride about being mexican but they also
share a pride about being oaxacan they share a pride about being mayan then you have mexicans with
different religious facets like all of this is imperative in identifying that these places are not
just one mass of people the difference is that they may have a shared understanding of their history
in a way that the united states does not because perhaps a different approach has been taking to
unifying the people whereas the approach here has always been about divide and conquer
sister seals this is your ancestor harriet tubman